http://www.beemaid.com/privacy-policy/

Bee Store
Store Locator
Honey Converter
Contact			About UsHoney MarketsOur ProductsRecipesThe BuzzHoney ProducersPrivacy PolicyBee Maid Honey Limited ("Bee Maid Honey") understands the importance of protecting your personal information.  Bee Maid Honey requires your name, address and email address in order to register contestants and to deliver prizes to winning entrants. Bee Maid Honey will use the personal information provided solely to administer the contest and to provide entrants with information concerning Bee Maid and its products or special offers from time to time. Bee Maid will not disclose or otherwise share the personal information provided to it in connection with the contest with any third party, unless required or permitted by law. Bee Maid maintains all personal information in accordance with its Privacy Policy, a copy of which can be found below. Should an individual no longer wish to receive information from Bee Maid, please advise the Bee Maid Privacy Officer in writing at honey@beemaid.com.All contest entrants must have read, agreed to and understood the Contest Rules in order to be eligible for entry.
Bee Maid Honey Limited Online Privacy Policy
IntroductionUse of the Bee Maid Honey E-Store, and any personal information provided to Bee Maid Honey Limited, the Alberta Honey Producers Cooperative Limited, and/or the Manitoba Cooperative Honey Producers Limited ("Bee Maid") in connection with use of the Bee Maid E-Store is subject to this Privacy Policy.Bee Maid is committed to protecting personal information under its control in accordance with its obligations at law, including The Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act of Canada.  Bee Maid has established this Privacy Policy to outline its privacy practices with respect to personal information provided in connection with its Website.Honey consumers who wish from time to time to receive recipes, Bee Maid's e-newsletter or coupons when available by e-mail must provide Bee Maid an e-mail address.  Bee Maid will not disclose any such personal information under its control to any third party without consent unless required or permitted by law.Privacy OfficerBee Maid has appointed a Privacy Officer to oversee its continued compliance with its privacy obligations at law.  Should any person have questions or concerns with respect to Bee Maid's Website Privacy Policy, its privacy practices or otherwise, our Privacy Officer may be contacted as follows:Privacy Officer
625 Roseberry Street
Winnipeg, MB R3H 0T4
Telephone:  (204) 786-8977
Toll Free: 1 866 788-8030
Facsimile:  (204) 783-8468
Email: honey@beemaid.comWhat is personal information?For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, the term “personal information” means information about an identifiable individual, but does not include the name, title, business address or business telephone number of an employee of an organization.  Information that does not identify specific individuals, such as aggregate statistics or anonymous data, is not considered to be personal information.Please note that this Privacy Policy applies to individual information only and does not apply to corporate information nor to publicly available information.What personal information does Bee Maid collect and what are the purposes for collection?To receive recipes and e-newsletters when available by e-mail, an e-mail address must be provided.  To improve and manage your use of the Bee Maid Website, Bee Maid may use cookies.  A cookie is an identification tag that our server gives your Web browser when you enter the site.  The cookie is used to note the state of your transaction and selections as you move through the Site.  When you shut down your Web browser, the cookie is deleted.  No information, personal or otherwise, is stored by Bee Maid on your computer once the session is completed.  Should you no longer wish to receive our communications by e-mail, simply unsubscribe or advise our Privacy Officer in writing.Changes to Personal InformationYou may update your personal information on file with Bee Maid by providing Bee Maid with notice in writing (by e-mail or otherwise) requesting the change.  Upon confirmation that such information should by amended, Bee Maid will attend to amending appropriate personal information.Use of Personal InformationOnly authorized employees of BeeMaid may have access to personal information.  Personal information may only be used by Bee Maid for the purposes for which it was submitted or for which a honey consumer has consented, unless required or permitted by law.Retention of Personal InformationBeeMaid will not retain personal information provided to it in connection with the Bee Maid Website following notice from the consumer that he or she no longer wishes to receive information from Bee Maid, unless otherwise required or permitted by law.  Bee Maid shall do so in a manner that continues to safeguard the confidentiality of the information.All personal information will be stored by Bee Maid in accordance with its obligations at law.  Bee Maid protects personal information using reasonable safeguards and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, use and disclosure.Disclosure of Personal InformationBee Maid does not disclose personal information to any third party without consent unless required or permitted by law.  In releasing personal information, Bee Maid will release the minimum amount of information required to comply with its obligations.Links to Other SitesOur Website contains resource links to other websites.  Bee Maid is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites or their operators.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of other sites they visit.Amendments to the Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time.  If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the changes to our website to notify you of these changes.  We will only use personal information collected after the changes are published for new purposes.  Please check back frequently.We will conduct periodic reviews of this Privacy Policy to make sure that it remains current with evolving client and member expectations, technologies and laws.Privacy PrinciplesBeeMaid adheres to the following privacy principles:AccountabilityBee Maid is accountable for all personal information under its custody or control and has appointed a Privacy Officer to monitor its compliance with its privacy obligations at law.  The Privacy Officer may appoint other individuals within Bee Maid to be responsible for the day-to-day collection and processing of personal information.Identifying PurposesThe purposes for which BeeMaid collects, uses and discloses personal information shall be identified at or prior to the time of collections.  Generally, Bee Maid requires personal information to establish and administer honey consumer accounts (if any) and to distribute recipes, its e-newsletter, coupons and other information from time to time concerning the honey industry, Bee Maid's products and services, and special offers and discounts.  Should Bee Maid need to use personal information for a new purpose, it shall obtain consent from the subject individual.
Bee Maid does not sell, rent or authorize access to any personal information collected about or from honey consumers to third parties. ConsentBeeMaid only collects, uses and discloses personal information with the knowledge and consent of honey consumers, except where required or permitted by law.  The type of consent required (namely the requirement to receive express or implied consent) will vary according to the sensitivity of the information.For greater certainty, Bee Maid may collect, use or disclose personal information without knowledge or consent subject to applicable laws, for example if seeking the consent of the individual might defeat the purpose of collecting, using or disclosing the information, such as in the investigation of a breach of an agreement or a contravention of a law, then no consent would be required.  Bee Maid may also collect, use or disclose personal information without consent to collect a debt, to comply with a subpoena, warrant or other court order, or as may be otherwise required or authorized by law.Limiting CollectionCollection of personal information is limited to that which is required to fulfill the purposes identified by Bee Maid.  Information shall be collected by fair and lawful means.Limiting Use, Disclosure and RetentionWe will only retain personal information for as long as is reasonably necessary.  Generally, Bee Maid retains personal information (namely e-mail addresses) of honey consumers until the consumer informs Bee Maid that he or she no longer wishes to receive information, at which time the personal information is deleted from our database.  This retention period may extend beyond the end of a honey consumer's relationship with us when it is required by law, or when it is reasonably necessary for us to have personal information to respond to any issues arising out of our relationship that may need to be addressed at a later date.We may provide personal information to other persons only:when we have an individual's consent, whether express or implied;when we are required or permitted by law to do so, or when we need to disclose the information to protect our interests in the context of a legal or administrative proceeding.AccuracyBee Maid shall make reasonable efforts to keep personal information accurate, complete and up-to-date.  If you find any errors in the personal information Bee Maid has about you, advise Bee Maid accordingly and Bee Maid will make the appropriate corrections.  Bee Maid will also communicate the corrected information to anyone it may have misinformed.  For personal information that remains in dispute, Bee Maid will make a note of your opinion in our records. At any time, individuals can inform our office, in writing, of changes to his or her personal information.  It is the responsibility of the Privacy Officer (or their designate) to ensure that these changes are made in our database where appropriate.SafeguardsBee Maid shall protect personal information with safeguards and security appropriate to the sensitivity of the information.  Such security measures shall protect against unauthorized access, use, disclosure, copying or modification. All Bee Maid's suppliers and agents, as part of their contracts with Bee Maid, are bound to maintain confidentiality and may not use personal information for any unauthorized purpose.    When Bee Maid provides personal information in response to a legal inquiry or order, Bee Maid takes steps to ensure that the order is valid and will disclose only the information that is legally required.All Bee Maid staff have been advised of Bee Maid's privacy obligations and policies.  Staff are only granted access to consumer personal information in order to complete their employment duties.OpennessBee Maid shall make readily to individuals specific information about its policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. Questions regarding our Privacy Policy can be directed to our Privacy Officer.Individual AccessUpon request, individuals shall be informed of the existence, use and disclosure of his or her personal information and shall be given access to that information.  An individual shall be able to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and have it amended as appropriate.  All of the foregoing being subject to exceptions specified at law.An individual may be required to provide sufficient information to permit Bee Maid to provide an account of the existence, use and disclosure of personal information.  The information provided shall be used only for this purpose.BeeMaid shall respond to an individual’s request for access within a reasonable time (namely by no later than 30 days following receipt of the request in writing).Challenging ComplianceAn individual shall be able to address a challenge concerning compliance with these privacy principles to the Privacy Officer.  The Privacy Officer shall investigate and respond to all complaints.  If a complaint is found to be justified, Bee Maid shall take appropriate measures, including, if necessary to amend its policies and practices.
If your concerns are not resolved to your satisfaction, you may consider contacting the Privacy Commissioner of Canada at the following address:Office of the Privacy Commissioner
112 Kent Street
Ottawa, Ontario
www.privcom.gc.ca
Newsletter Signup
Careers
Contact
Privacy Policy			625 Roseberry StreetWinnipeg, ManitobaCanada, R3H 0T4Phone: 204-786-8977Toll free: 1-866-788-8030Fax: 204-783-8468×Hungry for honey recipes?Get sweet meal ideas sent straight to your inboxEmail Address First Name Last Name Custom Signup Source About UsHistoryQuality CommitmentsIn The CommunityHoney MarketsFood ServiceIndustrialInternationalPrivate LabelOur ProductsCanadian ProductsInternational ProductsRecipesBreakfastHoney Banana Bread Overnight OatsBreakfast Pizza with Honey DoughCinnamon Honey Sauce for French ToastHoneyed Pecans and Chocolate Overnight OatsHoney Berry Roller-UpsApple Honey MuffinsRaspberry JamHoney Bran MuffinsBanana Raisin MuffinsBread Machine Honey Steel Cut Oats BreadCinnamon Honey Glazed Sticky BunsBlueberry Honey Overnight OatsHoney WafflesHoney Bacon BenedictHoney Smoothie BowlHoney Chia Seed PuddingHoney PancakesHoney Breakfast LoavesStrawberry CrepesBeveragesBanana DaiquiriChai Honey TeaFrosty Honey LatteHoney Hot Ginger TeaMojito HonitoBlueberry DelightBreakfast ShakeHoney LemonadeHoney Hot ChocolateHoney Coconut ColadaHoney Pumpkin LatteGlazed Pear MartiniHoney Lemon Mint Iced TeaBees Knees CocktailHoney Coffee LatteHoney Apple Crisp CocktailHoney Coconut Breeze MocktailIrish Honey CocktailHoney MargaritaRed SangriaAppetizers & Side DishesWhipped Cashew and Honey RicottaHealthy Picnic SaladFig & Goat Cheese Crostini with Honey Balsamic GlazeHoney Garlic Cauliflower BitesHoney Cucumber SaladHoney Citrus Fruit SaladHoney Glazed Red Pepper with Goat CheeseRoasted Spaghetti Squash with Honey ButterHoney Glazed CarrotsHoney Baked Veggie FriesHoney Roasted VegetablesHoney Carrot SoupHoney Roasted NutsHoney SlawHoney Soy Glazed AsparagusHoney Garlic Roasted BroccoliMushroom, Honey & Thyme Pastry BitesChicken Lentil Salad with a Honey Garlic DressingSauces & DressingsHoney BBQ SauceAll-Purpose Honey Teriyaki SauceHoney Mustard DressingHoney Mustard Dipping SauceHot Salted HoneyHoney Lemon DressingDessertsPeanut Butter and Honey Fudge BarsPecan Butter TartsCaramel ApplesBrowniesBittersweet Chocolate Raspberry CupcakesChocolate Peanut Butter ChewsHot Buttered Apple ToddyHoney Almond BiscottiBaklavaHoney Yogurt PopsiclesHoney Pumpkin CakeQueen Bee Apple PieChocolate PuddingCarrot CakePeach CobblerRhubarb Honey CrispDinnerSweet and Savoury Sloppy JoesTeriyaki Turkey WingsHoney Sriracha Slow Cooker MeatballsHoney Mustard SalmonHoney Lime Chicken SkewersHoney Garlic MeatballsHoney BurgersHoney BBQ Shredded PorkBaked Honey HamApricot Glazed ChickenEasy Honey Chicken WingsAsian Honey-Tea Grilled PrawnsHoney Garlic Beef Stir FryHoney ChiliHoney Crusted ChickenGrilled Chicken Salad with Strawberries, Avocado & BrieHoney Lime Chicken TacosCordon Blu Honey SkewersBBQ Pork SteaksOrange Honey BBQ RibsBaked GoodsVanilla Honey CakeHoney Peanut Protein BitesHoney Glazed DonutsHoney Cream Cheese IcingHoney Oatmeal CookiesChocolate Chip CookiesBee Nutty Choco-Chips CookiesAmbrosia Coffee CakeHoney Fruit CakeSunny Honey Cake"Busy-Bee" Coconut Honey Rum CakeHoney Carrot Snacking CakeApplesauce CookiesHoney Oat Quick BreadHoney Chocolate Bundt CakeCranberry, Spice & Honey CookiesHoliday Honey Ginger BreadHoney Ginger Snap CookiesGranola BarsHoney BagelHoney Beer BreadGraham CrackersBanana BreadLemon Poppy Seed SconesButtermilk Honey BiscuitsHealth & BeautyMoisturizing Cranberry Lip BalmSweetheart's Chocolate Honey ScrubHoliday TreatsTempThe BuzzSweet Facts - FAQHow do I store my honey?Do your bottles contain BPA?Does pure honey crystallize?Does honey spoil?Why pasteurize honey?What is pasteurized and unpasteurized honey?How do you make creamed honey?Why is my creamed honey hard?3 Sweet & Spooky Honey Recipes for Halloween5 Easy Honey Recipes for Back to School3 Easy Instant Pot or Slow Cooker Honey Recipes for Busy WeeknightsFrom Bee to BottleBee InformedQuality Canadian HoneyHow Do Bees Help The Environment?Honey - Part of a Healthy LifestyleHoney - The Healthy ChoiceEasy Ways to Help Pollinators!Pollinator Friendly FlowersBreakfast Ideas with HoneyHoney ProducersAlberta Honey Producers Co-operativeManitoba Cooperative Honey ProducersMember News Updates
Bee Store
Store Locator
Honey Converter
Contact
